[wind howling]
[engine revving]
SHARED FATE
[man 1] I hope there's a nice girl.
[woman 1] I want to fall in love.
[woman 2]
That's definitely a Japanese tattoo.
[woman 3] I haven't had much luck
with love until now.
Are there any young, handsome men
who would want to go out
with a couple of old ladies like us?
- Who are you calling an old lady?
- You're the only one here.
This brat always has to talk back.
- [man 2] It's about time I settled down.
- [man 3] I want a girl on this motorcycle.
[man 4]
The second time was also for assault.
I was a… marijuana dealer.
[interviewer] As I mentioned before,
this time, everyone's participation
will be contingent on submitting
to a drug test beforehand.
- [man 5] Looks are important.
- [man 6] I'd lay down my life.
[woman 4] I don't wanna be looked down on.
- [woman 5] I wanna kill men like that.
- [woman 6] Massacre them.
[man 1] I'll show them.
[man 2] I'm off.
LOVE
[opening theme song playing]
A MAN IN LOVE HAS NO FEAR. THE BADASS WAY.
BEGIN WITH A FIGHT, END WITH HONOR.
LET LOVE BLOOM. THE BAD BITCH WAY.
MEN AND WOMEN ONCE FEARED FOR BEING BAD
WILL REVEAL THEIR ALL
AND CHALLENGE FIGHT FOR THEIR LOVE
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
[dramatic music playing]
I got my first tattoo when I was 16.
When I get angry,
it's like I can't stop myself.
I lose track of my surroundings.
If someone looks down on me,
I'll sink them in the ocean.
I'm Taisei. I'm 22 years old,
born in Hiroshima and raised in Tokyo.
I can make any girl fall for me.
Honestly, it's a piece of cake.
There's no one here.
Okay.
[rap music playing]
If there's trouble in Kyoto,
I'm the one to call.
I always charge ahead.
We'd gather in the mountains
and fight it out sometimes.
Stun guns, batons, Molotov cocktails…
we used anything.
I'm Leo Yamamoto, 25 years old.
I'm from Kyoto.
I'm really hoping to fall in love.
I want to have a big adult romance.
That'd be great.
Sorry I'm late.
All good.
- Nice to meet you. What's up?
- You too. Hey.
- Let's fall in love.
- Yeah.
- I can fall in love, fight, whatever.
- Yeah?
[rap music playing]
I'm an ex-Self-Defense Force
yankii rapper.
I got fired from the Self-Defense Force
for driving without a license
and speeding.
I got arrested,
but I jumped out of the police car
while it was moving and ran away.
I'm 29 years old,
I'm from Kanagawa, and my name is Ari.
My friends call me Ari the Buddha.
[laughing]
Like, I'm clearly Ari the Buddha.
Can you imagine me angry?
If there's girls, I'm gonna snatch 'em up.
Wow, those tattoos are sick.
A rapper?
A rapper.
- Nice to meet you.
- [Ari] You too.
You good?
[Ari] I'm amazing.
[exhales deeply]
[rap music playing]
I used to get into fights,
like, three or four times a week.
I also became the leader of a biker gang.
BIKE GANG LEADER IN KYUSHU
I've been in a couple
of juvenile rehabilitation programs.
I was in prison for about three years.
2 TIMES IN JUVIE
3 YEARS IN PRISON
I'm Mizuki Noguchi.
I'm 27 years old.
From Kurume City, Fukuoka.
I have 40 or 50 ex-girlfriends,
give or take.
What are you looking at?
- Huh?
- Huh? Wanna fight?
Yeah?
You wanna go? Huh?
Come on! Come on!
Let's do it!
Come on! What you got?
[Bo] What the hell?
You kneed me, you bastard!
You used your knee!
- [Bo] Huh?
- Hey.
Yeah, bring it.
[Leo] I'm gonna remember that.
[rap music playing]
I just was in a bike gang in my hometown,
then I was a petty thug,
and then a yakuza.
I'd go to Nerima Station to buy guns.
We were all packing.
The reason I went straight
was for my family
or specifically because
I wanted to be with my kid.
I don't have much confidence in romance.
I'm Masaya Oda. I'm 28 years old.
I work as a fighter and stuff.
A SHY EX-YAKUZA
When it comes to girls,
it takes me a while
to make the first move, you know?
[laughs] It's hard for me.
What, it's all guys?
- What the hell?
- [Leo] Just us so far.
- It's all guys.
- Yeah?
- What's with you? Why are you staring?
- What? Huh?
- What the hell?
- You wanna go?
Do you? Huh?
- Come at me.
- You come at me.
- Well, you asked for it.
- What the hell?
Hey.
- Hey.
Huh? You wanna go?
Are you serious right now? Huh?
- What?
- You punk.
You want this? Bring it on. Eh?
Hey, maybe we can just sit.
- [clears throat]
- [exhales deeply]
[rap music playing]
I haven't had many normal relationships.
Most of them were pretty extreme.
I only really have
an elementary school education.
I rode off into the dawn on a stolen bike
when I was 14.
A year earlier than Ozaki did it.
My name is Asuka Oguri.
I'm from Nagoya City.
I run bars and stuff.
Right now, I'm the number one hostess
at a hostess bar in Nagoya.
I want to find a good man,
have a little fling, something fun.
A YOUTHFUL ROMANCE WITH THE BEST MAN
As long as his personality is really good,
I don't care
if his face looks like sludge.
If there's someone I don't like,
I might just beat them up.
Excuse me.
- Oh, she's cute.
- Whoa.
- [Assun] Where do I go?
- [Ari] That back tattoo is amazing.
- I'm Assun. Nice to meet you.
- [Tai-chan] Hi.
- [Leo] Hey there.
- She's international.
- [Assun] International? [laughs]
- [all laugh]
- I'm super Japanese.
- [Ari] Japanese?
- Yes. [chuckles]
- [Ari] Oh, really?
[rap music playing]
My real dad was a drug dealer.
I was in an environment
where it was my job to carry syringes.
My mom was a total yankii.
All my exes have been yankii,
drivers for the yakuza, and so on.
I've been super popular.
In the end,
I'll make everyone fall for me.
I'm Hikaru. I'm 23 years old.
I'm from Kawasaki in Kanagawa.
I'm hoping to find my husband here.
There better be some manly men.
Excuse me.
[Ari] Good morning.
- [Hikaru] Good morning.
- [Assun] Good morning.
[Hikaru] Nice to meet you.
[Ari] We got a blondie.
- [giggling]
- [Ari] Amazing.
[grunts]
What'll the next flavor be?
[rock music playing]
No joke, I'm super short-tempered.
If someone does something
I don't like, I point it out.
All 30 of my ex-boyfriends were abusive.
It was normal for me to have a knife
pointed at me, get punched in the face.
I've almost been killed.
They'd tell me to die with them.
Marina Takaoka, 25 years old.
And I'm from Osaka.
I thought getting hit
was a sign of affection.
So I'm looking forward
to finding true love.
[laughs] So scary.
- Another international one.
- [all laugh]
- [Maririn] So scared.
- [Hikaru] Is she Japanese?
Half-Japanese, definitely.
- From where?
- I'm half Iranian-French.
- Huh? Wait, did you say?
- [women laugh]
[Maririn] Okay, I get it. Oh, my God.
[Hikaru] That's so funny.
[rap music playing]
There was a festival in my hometown,
and there was a fight.
So I just snapped.
I cracked a few heads with a Zima bottle.
I don't think I can be into anyone
who isn't an alpha.
All my exes have been bad boys.
They were all bad boys. Swear to God.
I still cheat on them, though.
I really do cheat on them.
My name is Ruru Tanaka. I'm 26 years old.
I was born in Shizuoka.
I want to fall in love with someone
who I know I'll never let go of.
- What? This is crazy!
- [Ari] Whoa!
All these girls are international.
- [Ruru sighs]
- She's not international.
- Definitely not international.
- Okay, hold on.
I'm surprised. Everyone is
so much badder than I thought.
- Of course. Badder.
- [Assun] Badder?
- Hey.
- [Ruru] Nice to meet you.
What kind of half are you?
- Half? Oh, I'm a pure Japanese.
- [Leo] Pure Japanese.
- [Ruru] Oh, wow. This is so hype.
- [bell chiming]
[boy on PA]
Everyone, please introduce yourselves.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Yay.
- Yeah, let's get it. I'll go first.
- [Ruru] Yay!
[Ari] Yay.
♪ From the 0422
Representing Kanagawa, Sagami ♪
[Hikaru] You're a rapper!
♪ I'm the president of Sagami, Ari
Nice to meet you! Ra! ♪
Whoo! Yay!
[Ari] Uh, I like girls…
ARI (29)
KANAGAWA - RAPPER/MODEL
- …with blonde hair.
- Hmm? [chuckles]
- [Ari] Yeah, blonde.
- [Assun] Full of blondes here.
- This is awkward.
- What else?
- I like girls with a snaggletooth.
- Oh, I have one!
[women laugh]
- [Ruru] Whoo! That's right!
- A couple is born already.
- A couple is born.
- [Ruru] Okay.
[Ari, Assun, and Ruru] Nice to meet you.
[all applauding]
MARIRIN (25)
OSAKA - BAR WORKER
Uh, hey, you can call me Maririn,
and I work at a bar in Osaka.
- Ooh. Osaka.
- [Ruru] Ooh.
[Leo] Yeah!
LEO (25)
KYOTO - BAR OWNER
My name is spelled L-E-O, Leo.
For work, I run a bar in Kyoto.
- He's a go-getter.
- [Leo] Nice to meet you.
ASSUN (30)
AICHI - ENTREPRENEUR/HOSTESS
I'm Assun.
- [Ari and Leo] Assun?
- [Assun] Yes.
Uh, I'm probably the oldest one here.
- Well, I'm 30.
- [Leo] Oh, 30.
- Classic model.
- [Assun] I'm 30 and a half.
I like manly men.
Like the first letter of "kanji."
- [Hikaru] "Kan" of kanji.
- That one. That's the kind of man I like.
- Nice to meet you.
- Okay. Nice to meet you.
- Uh, my job is a fighter.
- [Hikaru] Ooh.
MA-KUN (28)
GUNMA - MMA FIGHTER
My type of girl is one with a cute face.
Uh, I hate people who don't make sense.
That's all.
[laughs] That was cool.
You're next.
Knock 'em dead, donkey face.
[women laugh]
BO
- Ouch.
- [Ma-kun] Are you okay?
- [Leo] He's running into things.
- [Ma-kun] You're nervous.
- Slow down.
- [Ma-kun] Why are you flustered?
- Are you nervous?
- He's already losing it.
- [Hikaru] That's cute.
- [Ma-kun] You're funny.
- [Assun] Boy.
- So, are you called Bo?
That's right. My type of woman is…
BO (27)
FUKUOKA - COMMERCIAL PAINTER
Well, as long as she has
a strong sense of self.
- Oh!
- [Bo] Nice to meet you.
RURU (26)
TOKYO - MODEL
My name is Ruru.
I work as a model.
I like guys who are manly
and have nice tattoos. [giggles]
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice.
My nickname is Tai-chan.
TAI-CHAN (22)
TOKYO - HAIRSTYLIST
I'm a hairstylist.
- Ooh!
- So unexpected!
[Tai-chan] I'm 22.
And I'd say
my type of girl is a flashy girl.
[Ruru] Oh.
My name is Hikaru. Nice to meet you.
HIKARU (23)
KANAGAWA - HOSTESS
I'm 23 years old.
And I'm a sucker for a gentleman.
- Nice to meet you.
- [Ari] Yeah!
Gentleman, huh?
[boy on PA] Attention.
Please show your true selves,
face your past,
and learn about love with all your might.
If you work hard,
a new version of yourselves
will be waiting for you
at the end of this journey.
Please make sure you follow the rules.
DON'T BE LATE. NO DRUGS. NO THEFT.
Above all, you may be expelled
if you act in a violent way toward someone
and hurt them.
NO EARLY CONFESSION. NO SEXUAL ACTS.
Did they make you take a drug test?
- [Ma-kun] I took one.
- Me too.
- What kind of dating show does that?
- [all laughing]
- [Hikaru] This one does.
- [Ma-kun] You're gonna get expelled.
I know I will.
- For real.
- I know it.
I feel like I can get along
with everyone for once.
And with that, Badly in Love 2 has begun.
NAGANO
- Glad to be with you.
- Thank you.
- Awich is here.
- [Nagano] Welcome.
- We'll be counting on you this time.
- Thank you.
[Megumi] I feel like
hip-hop people tend to be more aggressive.
And you're in a good place
to understand that.
Like, this guy
was about to release a song,
- but he got arrested.
- [Nagano exclaims]
So the man I married,
he was in prison for eight years.
- [exclaims]
- Even after he got out, he was in and out.
Our house was shot at.
- [Megumi] What?
- Huh?
- Your house?
- Like, "Bang, bang, bang."
- So I had to crawl on the floor…
- [Nagano] Oh.
- …just to get around my house.
- [Nagano] Oh, my.
- My daughter was a baby at the time.
- Oh.
She was sleeping in her bed,
so I had to drag her out of bed
and wait for it to stop.
- Seriously?
- Hold on, you're gonna upstage these kids.
Like, these participants' lives
are nothing
compared to what you've been though.
I'm so sorry.
So this time around,
these five men and four women
will be living together for two weeks.
At the end, they'll confess their feelings
at the graduation ceremony.
[bell chiming]
[boy on PA] Your first group activity
is making dinner in the kitchen.
All right!
- [Nagano] Ari is nice.
- [Megumi] They're excited.
LOVE DINER
- [Ruru] Cute.
- [Ari] Wow!
- [Assun] You're so loud.
- Wow!
- Wait! It's so cute!
- Oh, wow!
- Wow, this is crazy!
- This is amazing!
- A signature Okinawa A&W!
- What is this? It's amazing!
- [Hikaru] Super cute.
- [Ari] Burger King or something!
[Ruru] No, it's an A&W!
- [Leo] Wow.
- [Ruru] This is next level.
LOVE DINER
So freakin' cute, you guys!
- This is yankii approved.
- [Maririn] Right.
- [Leo] Super stylish.
- There are ingredients for curry.
I volunteer to cut the vegetables!
- Huh? Bo, you can't cook rice, can you?
- Sure, I can.
[Ruru] Then cook the rice, Bo.
What can you do?
- Um, vegetables.
- You can cut them?
- We'll cut together.
- Let's cut them.
- Want yellow or red?
- I want purple.
You want purple?
I've been told
purple is a color for horny people.
- Isn't it cute? I like purple the best.
- It is cute, for sure.
- She didn't deny it.
- What'd you say?
- Didn't deny she's horny.
- What?
Never mind.
Wow, they open up so fast!
- They really do.
- [Megumi] Indeed.
- This isn't the fourth day, right?
- No, it's not.
- So, you're a model and…
- Right. I'm just a model.
- Just a model?
- Yeah.
- Nuts Agency?
- Oh, yeah! I'm with them.
- What is it?
- Oh, I just think you're cute.
Really? I like that.
Lady Ruru.
TAI-CHAN (22)
HAIRSTYLIST
Lady Ruru really… blew me away.
- [Nagano] In love already?
- Her face is too beautiful.
It's so cute and small.
When she asked me
to do vegetables together,
I felt like in that moment, I won.
[Nagamo] This kid moves fast.
This is definitely better.
LEO (25)
BAR OWNER
Wow, those are some fancy knife skills.
- Don't make fun of me.
- [laughs]
- You seem like a man who can use a knife.
- [chuckles] I'm trying my best.
Amazing.
It's crazy, you give off
such Kansai-person vibes.
- Me?
- It's a good thing.
- I like the Kansai dialect.
- You do?
Yeah, I love it.
- They have all kinds of alcohol.
- [Hikaru] I can't drink alcohol.
- Can't drink?
- Even though I'm a hostess.
- Not one drop?
- Nope, I'm allergic.
- So, what do you do at work?
- I have soft drinks.
- Oh, so that's how it is. Uh-huh.
- Uh-huh.
Do we simmer this?
Whatever. Let's just have a smoke.
- Let's do that.
- Let's go.
Impromptu smoke break.
Know that this dating show
will have a lot of smoking scenes.
- [Ruru] Let's go have a smoke.
- Okay, keep cooking. I'll be right back.
[Ruru] Where's the smoking area?
- [Leo] You're older than me?
- [Ruru] I'm 26.
- Do you like younger girls?
- No, I've only dated older girls.
[Ruru] Oh, really?
Here is fine.
- [Awich] Oh, so Ruru is older.
- [Megumi] That's right.
- [Ruru] How many girlfriends have you had?
- [Leo] About five or six.
Ah. You dumped them, right?
Honestly, no.
You'd think so, but I get dumped.
- Why? You're a cheater?
- No, I don't cheat.
What'd you do then?
My relationship to my friends comes first.
Oh, I see.
Often, I had to drop everything
and go somewhere for them.
Oh, I really like that.
I like guys who value their friends.
I like them better than other guys
who only focus on their girlfriends.
It's more fun that way.
Like, you can take her along with you.
- Absolutely.
- Like, for dinner.
If anything, I would want to meet them.
- Right.
- To hang out with them.
- Ruru has so much energy, doesn't she?
- Well, she did say she cheats.
- [Nagano] That's true!
- She must be confident.
[Megumi] Right.
- [Ruru] How's the food?
- [Ma-kun] It's done.
- [Leo] It's tasting great.
- [Ruru] Then let's eat!
Let's serve the rice too.
- [bell chiming]
- Huh?
[Ruru] There's an announcement.
[boy on PA]
To all of you who like alcohol…
- [Ruru] Yay!
- I love it!
[Maririn] I like it. That's me.
…whether you get to drink alcohol today
is up to all of you.
- [Ruru] What does that mean?
- [Leo] That's crazy!
[boy on PA] If you can cooperate
and complete the task assigned to you,
you can have alcohol with dinner.
If you fail…
- [Ruru] Huh? No way!
- …there will be no alcohol.
- [Leo] Seriously?
- [Ruru] I definitely want to drink!
Alcohol is
the one important thing in life.
- [laughs] My goodness.
- [Awich] So cool.
I might like her.
ASSUN (30)
ENTREPRENEUR/HOSTESS
I wonder how much I drink in a day.
Well, if we're talking about whiskey,
I drink a whole bottle.
[boy on PA]
Everyone, please move to the gym.
- [Leo] Let's go.
- What are we gonna do?
- It's just a regular gym.
- [Assun] What's the task?
- [Maririn] For real?
- [Assun] A jump rope.
- [Ruru] It's girly!
- [Maririn] It sparkles!
[Ari] Are those spikes? Let's see it.
[boy on PA] Your task
is to jump rope 30 times in a row.
You only have one chance.
- [Ruru] What?
- [Tai-chan] Whoa, 30 times.
- [Ruru] Thirty?
- [Leo] Thirty times in a row? Jeez.
[Ma-kun] That's crazy.
- Here we go. Ready, set…
- [Maririn] Ready, set…
[all] 1, 2, 3, 4…
[Nagano] You'd never think
they were fighting earlier.
- …7, 8, 9…
- [Megumi] They're cute, aren't they?
- [Nagano] They are.
- …10, 11, 12, 13…
- [Hikaru shrieks]
- [Megumi] Oh, geez.
No. I wanted to drink.
- [Ruru] Please! Give us another chance!
- [Hikaru] Who was it? Who tripped?
This happened
because they didn't practice.
- They could have practiced.
- [Megumi] Right?
They went at it without even warming up.
Please give us another chance!
We only need one more!
- We promise!
- [boy on PA] No drinks for you today.
- I'm dead.
- Me too.
- [Ruru] One more chance!
- [Leo] No second chances?
It was going so well!
I think if we just set our minds to it,
we can get it done.
- Yeah.
- We've got to make them let us try again.
- [laughs]
- [Awich] They're not giving up.
If we get down on our knees and apologize…
- We're yankii.
- [Ma-kun] Yeah.
- Don't underestimate us. We can do it.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
- Wait, you're doing it?
- We're begging you.
- We're sorry.
- [Nagano] Why are they looking at us?
- Give us another chance!
- Please!
- [Nagano] This feels wrong.
[all] Please!
- [Ma-kun] Please!
- [Leo] We'll be good.
[Ma-kun] We'll really be good.
I've never bowed down on my knees
in my whole life.
I'm surprised at what I'm capable of
if alcohol's on the line. [laughs]
We'll be good, for real.
- [boy on PA] All right, one more chance.
- [all cheering]
- [Nagano] Seriously?
- [Megumi] It's their first day.
- [Assun] We did it!
- [Ruru] Let's do our best!
- [Maririn] All right.
- Wait, let's huddle up.
- All right. Last one.
- This is our last chance.
- This is our final chance.
- [Ruru] Our final chance. Let's huddle up.
- [Ari] Bring it in.
- Let's jump this rope!
- Come on!
- [all] Let's go!
We can do it, we can do it, we can do it!
- Let's do our best. Thirty times.
- Let's go!
- [Hikaru] Here we go.
- [Ari] We got this.
- Thirty times, right?
- Here we go.
- [Ari] Be strong!
- [Bo] All right.
Here we go. Ready, set…
[Maririn and Ruru] 1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7, 8,
9, 10, 11, 12,
13, 14, 15, 16,
17, 18, 19, 20, 21…
- [Awich] They're gonna do it.
- [Nagano] They just might. Here it comes!
…25, 26, 27, 28,
29, 30!
- We did it!
- [all cheering]
- [Nagano chuckles] No, what is this?
- [Ruru] We did it!
[Nagano]
What is this sense of accomplishment?
- We have a whole season of episodes first.
- [Assun] We did it!
We are totally badass.
- [panting] That was crazy.
- [Ma-kun] That was insane.
[Ruru] I feel like we're closer now
because of that. What a moment.
- [Ma-kun] I'm glad we did it.
- [Ruru] Right?
I didn't do that stuff
when I was a student.
So I'm living my youth now.
The last time I jumped rope
was a year and a half ago
at a sports festival…
in prison.
Bo says he hasn't jumped rope
since the prison sports festival.
- He's been in and out.
- [Nagano] No way.
- [boy] Time for dinner.
- [Ari] Let's drink.
The alcohol is in the living room.
This is so sick. Oh, my God.
- Oh, look at this!
- [Ruru] Oh, so cute!
- This is amazing!
- Incredible.
[Ari] I can't believe my eyes right now.
- This is wild.
- Wow!
- [Ari] Super cool.
- [Ruru] It's too cute!
[Maririn] I don't know how to read that.
"This life is all I need"?
- [Ari] The bonsai's huge!
- [Ruru] Cute!
- [Tai-chan] Amazing.
- [Ari] So cool!
- [Assun] I love it.
- [Ari] The art is amazing too.
[Ruru] This is the best.
- [Leo] I could get used to this.
- [Assun] Sick!
- Cheers!
- [all] Cheers!
- [Ari] Wassup?
- [Assun] Yeah.
- Let's eat.
- [Ma-kun] Thanks for the food!
- [Assun] Thank you for the food.
- Whoa, this is so good!
[Leo and Maririn] Delicious!
[Ari laughs] You're eating too fast.
Wait, Tai-chan is so cute.
- [Maririn] He's eating so much.
- [Leo] Don't you just want to feed him?
- [Ma-kun laughs] Right? So cute.
- [Leo] Look at him.
It's crazy, it's like maternal instinct.
You know, I think Bo is
the most mysterious guy here.
- [Hikaru] I can't read him.
- [Ruru] He doesn't talk much.
I really want to know
what has happened to him in his life.
At the end of my first year
of junior high,
I was sent to a juvenile assessment center
for beating up a friend.
[Leo exclaims]
Then, a year later,
I was sent to a juvenile training school.
Oh, so you were in there
for quite a long time.
- [Bo] Yeah, a long time.
- So you were barely out in the real world?
- [Leo] Barely out in your teens.
- [Ruru] Yeah.
- What about you, Ma-kun?
- Me?
[Ruru] You're another one
I can't read, Ma-kun.
- [Leo] He's the hardest for me to read.
- I'm pretty normal. I was in a bike gang.
Then became a normal thug,
a normal yakuza, then I quit normally.
- [Assun] All normal.
- [Ruru] What about your pinky?
I don't have it anymore.
- Seriously?
- [Maririn] You don't?
[Ma-kun] I don't.
- [Ruru] Oh, my God. I didn't notice.
- [Ma-kun] I don't.
So, yeah,
I just kept going down that path.
And then…
I had a kid.
And after I had a kid, I got arrested.
The time you spend with your kid,
when they're still small,
you only have that moment.
That made me think,
"This isn't right. I'm so lame."
So I said,
"I'm out. I'd rather be with my kid."
And then I started martial arts.
So yeah.
Wow, you are so manly.
You're almost too manly.
[Leo] You have a good personality.
That's why people are interested in you.
[Ruru] That's true.
Man, that story really hit me hard.
- [laughs]
- [Ruru] You're so cool.
- [Awich] The girls seem into him.
- [Megumi] Mmm.
I had a kid, and then, I went straight.
I started living a life
where I could go home.
But then, somehow,
things started going wrong.
So we decided to start over,
and we broke up.
And then, about six months and a bit ago,
she got remarried.
At that time, I also felt…
not so much refreshed, more like…
"Wow, I can finally move on."
And so, I came here.
My family situation was bad too.
I was always out
because I really didn't want
to be at home.
Like, since I was a kid,
my mom's boyfriend
would be pretty abusive.
When I was 3 or 4, I saw him
punch my mom right in front of me.
Like, he broke her skull and stuff.
She was really beaten up to a pulp.
And I was also beaten up sometimes.
- I want to kill this guy.
- [Ruru laughs]
For real, I had welts all over my body.
- Is he still alive?
- [Ruru] He's alive.
Then I'll kill him.
Like, yeah, it's true,
I had a pretty tough past. [laughs]
- [Assun] You don't have to laugh.
- Yeah, oh, yeah.
[Ma-kun] Not funny at all.
I really want to give you a hug right now.
- [Ruru laughing]
- [Megumi] Look, she's so sweet.
[Assun] I feel like crying.
[Leo] I think these girls
are "badly in love."
[laughter]
- [Ruru] Thank you, Assun.
- Are you okay? Really? Are you okay?
- I'm okay. I'm living strong now.
- You're strong. That's good.
- [Ruru] I'm alive and well.
- [Assun] I feel like crying so much.
- [Ruru] Wait, I want to hear your story.
- I think we're really alike.
- Oh, yeah?
- We're very similar.
We belong to the same group.
Like, my real dad,
I really don't know him,
but he was an abuser and a drug dealer.
And worse, because he was a drug dealer,
I went through many sad experiences.
So, I really crave company.
LIVE IN THE MOMENT
[Ari] That's deep. [inhales deeply]
- Hikaru, you're too deep.
- I'm too deep, right?
I'm just sorry…
I can't do anything about it.
- You can listen to me.
- Yeah. [laughs]
[Hikaru] I'm counting on you.
My ex-girlfriend, I can't forget her.
Yeah.
Like…
She keeps popping up
all the time in my mind.
So I can't move on to my next love.
I feel like my ex-girlfriend
cast a spell on me
so I can't fall in love with anyone else.
I have this old wallet
that I keep in my pocket.
My ex-girlfriend said,
"You can use this. I'll lend it to you."
So I borrowed it.
- And we broke up while I had it.
- [Megumi] He's completely worn it out.
I know I shouldn't use it.
Maybe that's why I can't forget her.
At some point soon, though,
I'd really like to escape from this
and move on to the next stage.
[Megumi] It sounds like
he's still hung up on her.
SMOKERS' LOUNGE
[Ruru] Bo?
- Huh? Where's Bo?
- [Bo] What's up?
Oh, God, I got drunk.
Will you listen to my story?
[Ruru] Bo.
- [Bo] You cold?
- [Ruru] Huh?
[Ma-kun] So kind.
A gentleman.
[Bo] So, you know,
my friend died last September.
- [Ma-kun] Mmm-hmm.
- My childhood friend.
[Ma-kun] Right.
Wait, hold on, tell me properly.
- You went to the same junior high, right?
- Same kindergarten.
Going into middle school,
we always had each other's backs.
Mmm.
And…
I got a call from a police officer
saying he was missing.
- I thought, "No way."
- Mmm.
And…
Well, I heard he was missing,
and I vaguely had a hunch.
[Ruru] Mmm.
And, you know,
my house was a hangout spot at the time.
So I went with my aniki
and my brothers to look for him.
[Ruru] Mmm.
But I…
I was scared.
I was scared to be the one to find him.
[Ruru] Mmm.
[Bo] So it happened.
And my route to work, well…
passes where my friend died.
Does that mean you saw him?
- [crying]
- [Ruru chuckles]
It's okay. That must have been hard.
That's painful.
[sniffles] If I'd only
realized it back then…
- [sniffles] So I still think about it.
- Mmm.
[sighs]
[sighs] It was the first time
I saw someone die.
[Ruru] I see.
If he knew I would be on this show,
he would have been so happy.
[Ruru] Oh, yes.
I'm sure he would have been.
I get it. I don't have
a childhood friend like that, but…
but I lost my aunt who I loved so much.
So I get it.
But you still have so many regrets, right?
- I do.
- You do?
I mean, like,
my mom and my home environment
weren't great, right?
So my mom's younger sister, my aunt,
because my home environment was so bad,
she would always move to a place nearby
so when things weren't good,
I could run away to her.
So I always had a safe place
that wasn't home.
- A place like that is important.
- Right.
And, yeah, with my aunt,
she had to go on dialysis and got sick.
And she passed away.
- Wanna sit?
- [both laugh]
Yeah, she passed away, but…
[voice breaking] I think about her a lot.
I think if I had taken her to the hospital
sooner, even if it was forcefully,
maybe she wouldn't have passed away.
- You're good.
- [chuckles softly]
- So yeah. [sniffles]
- You're a good girl.
I think about her a lot.
I really liked her so much. [sniffles]
That feeling of losing
someone you cherish,
I understand how much it hurts.
- Right? Human life is so fleeting.
- So fleeting. So fleeting.
Right? Seriously.
When someone passes, it's so fleeting.
- I wish I could have told her more things.
- Even saying goodbye is fleeting.
Right? It's all so fragile.
Seriously, the moment they go
into the fire, it's just so fleeting.
[sniffles]
- Like, death is so painful, right?
- Yeah, yeah.
But there are a lot of things
I learned from that experience.
Wow. Bo, you're the best. [laughs]
I'm sorry,
but this is the first episode, right?
[Megumi] Yes.
This is all happening on the first day.
Why did he suddenly open up like that?
- Right? Maybe…
- [Nagano] Maybe what?
Maybe all of them have been
living in such a harsh world.
- Okay.
- [Megumi] Mmm.
A world that doesn't follow the rules, so…
the men and women who live in that world,
they never know what's going to happen.
[Megumi and Nagano] Mmm.
Living there takes courage,
but they're also taking a lot of risks.
So they might suddenly not be able to
see each other anymore.
- I see.
- [Megumi] That can happen.
So you can see why they feel
their world is so fleeting.
When they connect
with people who understand that,
it just naturally comes out of them.
- [Nagano] It comes out suddenly.
- Their emotions.
I feel like
the show will end after two episodes.
- [laughs]
- I mean, seriously.
[bell chiming]
[boy on PA]
The bedrooms are separated by gender.
[Hikaru] Oh, no way!
- [Ruru] Wait, this is so cute.
- This is sick! Oh, my God, so great.
- This is amazing.
- Wow!
- It's so cute!
- This is the best!
- For real?
- [Hikaru] It's so cute.
- [Assun] I'm so hyped, girls, so hyped.
- [Hikaru] So sick.
[Ruru] Hey, wait, it's so yellow.
A happy yellow!
- [Maririn] Oh, wow, it's so cute.
- [Hikaru] It's so cute!
Hey, look, see that? "Madly in love."
- [Hikaru and Ruru] "Madly in love."
- [Hikaru] We have arrived!
- [Leo] We're over here?
- [Ma-kun] I can't wait to see it.
- [Tai-chan] Here I go.
- [Ma-kun] Let's go in.
I can already see it's amazing.
- This is crazy.
- Oh, my God.
- [Ari] What? How is it?
- It's amazing. So sick.
- Wow, it's so big.
- [Leo] Now we're talking.
- [Tai-chan] Amazing.
- [Leo] My God.
- [Ma-kun] So sick.
- [Tai-chan] This is massive.
- [Ma-kun] It's so cool.
- [Leo] It's so nice.
[Tai-chan] Incredible.
[Leo] I love it.
[Tai-chan] This is the best. So cool.
- It's so nice.
- [Ari] This is so insane.
- [Leo] Hell yeah!
- [Tai-chan] Wow, it's awesome!
[Ari] Is this okay?
It's scary.
No katanas, bro.
BADASS
BAD BITCH
[Ruru] I don't know about you girls, but…
don't you feel motivated
to open up and fall in love?
- [Hikaru] Mmm.
- [Assun] Oh, that's good.
The one I think has strong principles
would be Ma-kun.
Ah.
The one I want to get to know more
is Tai-chan.
[Ruru] Oh, really?
And the one that I think
is truest to his principles
is the same one you said.
[Ruru] Yeah, that's true.
That makes sense.
- Everyone would think that.
- [Ruru] That makes sense.
I mean, the people I've dated so far
have all been like that.
I mean, I really thought Ma-kun and I
were on the same wavelength.
- Mmm.
- [Ruru] That's what I thought.
You know who else?
- Leo. I think Leo is fun too.
- [all] Ah.
- And I really like funny guys.
- That Kansai dialect.
- [Assun] Yeah.
- But Ma-kun… is nice.
The four of us
are going to fight over him.
- [Ruru] What?
- [Assun] Over Ma-kun.
- [Ruru] I'm gonna go all out.
- [laughs] Today? On day one?
[Ruru] I'm gonna go all out,
but Ma-kun seems like
he likes older women.
- [Hikaru whispers] I know.
- [Ruru] But I'm not gonna lose.
- I'm not gonna lose.
- [Assun] I'm not gonna lose.
- I'm not.
- [Assun] I'm not gonna lose either.
Don't try to cover your face.
I'm not gonna lose.
- I'm not gonna lose.
- [Assun laughing]
I'm not gonna lose.
[bell chiming]
[boy on PA]
Now, each of you will write a love letter
- to the person you're interested in.
- [Ruru] Here it is.
Just one though?
[boy on PA]
Write a love letter anonymously
to the one person you felt something for…
[Assun] Oh?
…and put it in their mailbox
when you're done.
[Hikaru] Anonymously?
- [Nagano] Here we go.
- [Megumi] Who're they thinking of?
[sentimental rock music playing]
LEO
MA-KUN
YOU'RE THE ONE I'M…
TO TAI-CHAN
ASSUN, YOU'RE STRONG-WILLED
BY INSTINCT, I THOUGHT…
MA-KUN (28)
MMA FIGHTER
[Megumi] Who's getting Ma-kun's letter?
- [Nagano] Oh!
- [Megumi] Oh, it's Assun.
She looks out for people.
That consideration towards others
is something you're born with.
I felt she's someone who thinks like I do.
ARI (29)
RAPPER/MODEL
- [exhales deeply]
- [Nagano] What about Ari?
[Megumi] He put it in Hikaru's.
I haven't met anyone with blonde hair
and a snaggletooth in a while.
So I was like, "Wow, she's awesome."
I was like, "Should I confess to her
tomorrow or maybe today?"
BO (27)
COMMERCIAL PAINTER
- [Nagano] It's Bo.
- [Megumi] Bo.
[Nagano]
Bo's gonna give his letter to that girl.
- [Megumi] Ruru.
- [Nagano] Right?
[Bo] I wrote my letter
to this person called Ruru.
She seemed to value those close to her.
I felt she had a burning passion.
TAI-CHAN (22)
HAIRSTYLIST
RURU
Lady Ruru, man, that girl…
She and I need to talk, for real.
LEO (25)
BAR OWNER
[Nagano] What about Leo?
[Leo] Been a while
since I wrote a love letter.
[Nagano] Ah, he put it in Ruru's.
Because I like Ruru's face. It's cute.
Ruru's the one I liked the most today.
ASSUN (30)
ENTREPRENEUR/HOSTESS
[Nagano] What about Assun?
- [Megumi] Ma-kun, it's mutual!
- [Nagano] Ah!
He has the strongest backbone.
He's so firm.
I think he really has the kind
of personality that I like in a guy.
HIKARU (23)
HOSTESS
MA-KUN
He's the first letter in kanji.
He's an alpha.
Like, he's definitely the most popular.
MARIRIN (25)
BAR WORKER
[Nagano]
Maririn, who's she gonna give it to?
- Ooh!
- [Megumi] Tai-chan.
Everyone said Ma-kun,
but he looks so much like my ex,
and he was also a thug.
My thug ex-boyfriend took all my money.
Like, I had a flashback and got scared.
That might be why
I felt a bit more interested in Tai-chan.
[Nagano] Maririn seems a bit shy.
RURU (26)
MODEL
[Megumi] What about Ruru,
the most popular girl?
[Nagano and Megumi] Oh!
[Nagano] So that's how it is.
If there's a letter from Leo
in my mailbox,
then that's it, I'm going all in on him.
- [Nagano] All in, huh?
- If there isn't, we're done.
Like, fuck you. Just like that.
"Fuck you."
She knows what that means in English,
doesn't she?
So, as you can see,
- the romances are starting to take shape.
- [Nagano] Yes.
Ma-kun seems to be
very popular among the girls.
- They seem to like him.
- [Megumi] Mmm.
I think he's the scariest one
out of all the group.
[Megumi] Huh?
- Why do you say that? He seems nice.
- [Megumi] Right?
If he can keep up that nice attitude,
it means he doesn't have
to put on a tough face.
Ah.
So I think that deep down,
he may be really confident and strong.
- [Nagano] Right.
- [Megumi] Oh.
If well-channeled,
that can turn out to be a very good thing.
But if it goes in a bad direction,
I think it can be really scary.
- I see.
- [Nagano] Ah!
How do you know that? You're amazing.
And then, that same Ma-kun
wrote his letter to Assun, right?
- And Assun wrote back to Ma-kun.
- Mmm. Oh.
And Hikaru also wrote hers to Ma-kun.
And Ari wrote to Hikaru.
- And Maririn wrote to Tai-chan.
- Right.
Ruru got letters
from Leo, Tai-chan, and Bo.
- And Ruru wrote hers to Leo, right?
- [Nagano] Mmm.
So Ma-kun and Ruru
are very popular this time.
Yes, and they seem to have good matches
for themselves, don't they?
- Their interest is mutual.
- Ma-kun, yeah, but for Leo…
- I don't know.
- That's right.
In any case, Ruru is very confident.
- In herself.
[Megumi] Mmm, mmm.
And I think she wants to see
what other people are like first.
- [Megumi] Ah!
- Oh!
- She's strategizing. Ah.
- I think she has a strategy, for sure.
If that's true,
that would be interesting. I'm curious.
[Nagano] Hey, what's wrong, Bo?
Hey, what happened?
- [Tai-chan] Let's decide.
- [Bo] Two of us?
[Tai-chan] Yes, two of us.
Oh, are you okay?
- So-so. [chuckles]
- [Leo] Are you good?
My contact lenses.
My eye got injured from some liquid,
so I'm going to the hospital.
- What? Wait.
- [Megumi laughs]
- He even says it like a delinquent.
- He may be quite clumsy.
Seriously?
I'll pray for your safety.
- [Bo] Thanks.
- [Leo] Yeah.
- I'm getting really nervous.
- [Ma-kun] For real.
- I get that.
- [Leo] Right?
If you go first and come back
with a letter, I'll stab you.
- Why me?
- I mean it. Yeah.
- [Ari] I'm going to go.
- [Leo] Mmm.
[breathes deeply]
Smell you later.
[Leo] He looks so relaxed.
- [Megumi] I wonder if there is one.
- [Nagano] I see.
[Megumi] They'll pick up the letters.
Seriously? I don't wanna open it. [sighs]
[pleasant music playing]
Please let there be one.
- [Megumi] Zero.
- [Awich] Nothing.
[Tai-chan] Oh, he's back.
[Ma-kun] He must've gotten one.
- [Tai-chan] He got zero.
- Hello there.
You seem so confident.
You got one, didn't you?
[sighs]
- [Nagano] Oh!
- [Megumi] Ah!
- He's happy, I'm sure.
- [Nagano] Sure he is.
[humming]
[Megumi] Oh, Mr. Popular.
- Whoa.
- [Megumi] Ruru put hers in there.
LEO, YOUR KANSAI DIALECT
REALLY LIGHTENS THE MOOD!
LET'S HAVE FUN UNTIL THE LAST DAY
My heart is just like
Tom and Jerry right now.
It's going like, "Bum, bum, bum, bum."
This is more than just a "like."
It's love.
You're grinning so much.
- Congratulations.
- What?
- Am I that obvious?
- [Ari] You are.
- You're obvious, bro. So obvious.
- [Leo] Really?
[Ari] I didn't get any, you know?
- [Leo] Huh?
- I didn't get any.
But you got one,
you got another, and I got two.
Oh, did you figure out
who the message was from?
- I don't know.
- [Leo] I think Assun.
- Assun's is in here.
- [Leo] Yeah.
- Who do you think it's from?
- I think mine is from Ruru.
[Ma-kun and Tai-chan] Oh!
- [Leo] Hmm.
- Then who could mine be from?
- The only one left is Hikaru, right?
- Hikaru?
You suddenly become conscious of them.
- Don't you?
- [Leo] Yeah.
- [Tai-chan] You do?
- [Leo] Of who wrote it.
- [Ma-kun] Yeah.
- [Leo] You're conscious of them.
I'M MOST INTERESTED IN YOU.
- This is major.
- [Ma-kun] It really is.
- [Leo] A huge step forward.
- [Ma-kun] It really moves your heart.
- It's touching.
- [Ari] Makes you feel positive about love.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU MORE!
- [Leo] Yeah.
- [Ma-kun] Yeah.
[Ari] It makes you
look forward to falling in love.
Well, to be honest,
I don't know if the girl who wrote
a letter to me is really Hikaru.
But I think it's Hikaru.
But then, I also wrote a letter to Ruru.
So, for me,
I can't think of anyone else
other than those two.
That's where I'm at now.
Tai-chan's misunderstanding
is making him think
the love letter he received
was from Hikaru.
Now he thinks she's into him,
he's like, "Hikaru seems nice."
- Oh, so that's what's happening!
- Right. It was Maririn.
- That's right.
- He's got it wrong.
- Exactly.
- What a shame.
Yeah, right?
Congratulations.
Don't say "congratulations."
It's not like we're a couple already.
- You should move on.
- It's just beginning.
- Right?
- There's more time.
It's like going
from a rice bowl to a rice box.
I'm not sure I get that.
- Don't get it?
- [Leo] Nope.
Like going from a beef bowl
to a cheese beef bowl.
More like going from conveyor belt sushi
to high-end sushi.
Ooh!
- Like sushi in Ginza, huh?
- You're fired as a rapper.
- He's the rapper now.
- [laughs]
What do you mean? It was just an analogy.
[Megumi] Okay, it's the girls' turn.
[excitedly] Ooh!
I don't think I have any.
[gasps]
[giggles]
[giggling]
- [Megumi] And she's running.
- Oh, my goodness.
- She ran over here.
- [laughing]
We know what that means.
- Ta-da!
- [Ruru] Yay!
- I got a letter!
- [Nagano] She's adorable.
- [Megumi] So cute.
- That's so nice!
TO HIKARU: WASSUP! WHEN I FIRST SAW YOU
TODAY, I LOVED YOUR BLONDE HAIR
[Megumi] "Wassup."
She'll figure it out. He made it easy.
AND YOUR SNAGGLETOOTH IS JUST PERFECT TOO
[Awich] He even mentioned
the blonde hair and the snaggletooth.
- It's so cute.
- [Assun and Ruru] Oh!
- [Ruru] You're grinning!
- It's so packed.
- The whole paper.
- [Ruru] Really?
Yeah.
All of a sudden,
she has the face of someone in love.
- Okay, this is pretty hot.
- [all laughing]
I'm in heat. I feel like a woman.
[pensive rock music playing]
[Nagano] Oh, Maririn.
- Well, I'm back.
- [Ruru] Welcome back.
Who could it be?
Huh? Shall we do it? Shall we show them?
This is Leo.
- It's Leo.
- [Megumi] Girls can really tell.
[Hikaru] "To begin with, I'm not 35."
- [Ruru] This is from Tai-chan.
- Oh?
[Hikaru]
"I honestly thought you were cute."
"I want to talk to you more."
- [Assun] "You're cute."
- How do you know?
Because we were in the kitchen.
- This is Tai-chan.
- He said you're cute.
[Ruru] I don't know who this is.
- [Maririn] It's written vertically.
- [Hikaru] Isn't this Bo?
[Ruru] You also think it's Bo?
- [Maririn] How old is he?
- [Hikaru] "I live by my instincts."
- [Assun] Sounds like Bo.
- [Ruru] Does it?
So, Bo wrote it vertically, huh?
- Like a prisoner.
- [Megumi] Yeah.
No, prisoners also write horizontally.
- They do?
- How do you know?
How do you know?
[chuckling] There are also letters
written horizontally.
- That's Ma-kun.
- [Hikaru] Mmm-hmm.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's Ma-kun.
- [Hikaru] What does it say?
- [Maririn] I wanna see.
[Assun] "I like how you're a tomboy,
but you're also considerate of others."
"I also like how you look."
- [Ruru] Isn't that Ma-kun?
- [women] Aw!
Oh, I'm so happy.
- That's nice, isn't it?
- [Maririn] So sweet.
Isn't it so awesome
you got the one from Ma-kun?
So it's mutual for both of you.
- Huh? This guy?
- [Hikaru] That's right.
Oh, that's true.
- We don't know for sure yet.
- Yeah.
When I opened it,
there were three letters in there.
So I thought,
"There it is, I'm officially popular."
I'm on fire. Just like that.
- [Maririn] There they are.
- [Assun] They're here.
- Good morning.
- Hey, girls.
[Ari] Hey.
- I'm not seeing Bo here.
- Is he still not better?
- Not yet. He's at the hospital.
- [Hikaru] That bad?
I hope he's okay.
- He went to the hospital.
- I'm so worried.
None of you did this to him, right?
- Hmm?
- To Bo.
- No way.
- You didn't make his eyes swell up?
- Oh, he's here.
- [Ruru] He's back.
- [Ma-kun] There he is.
- I'm back.
- [Assun] Welcome back.
- [Hikaru] What a cool entrance!
- [Leo] You got jumped.
- Yeah, right.
- Leo did this while I slept.
- I what?
- [Bo laughs]
- I knew it.
- [Leo] Hey.
- [Ruru] You okay?
- It was my contacts.
- [Ruru] Aw.
- [Ari] I'm glad you made it back.
- Yeah.
Bo, you didn't get any letters.
Don't feel bad.
- I get it, I get it. [laughs]
- [bell chiming]
[boy on PA] It's the afternoon sauna time.
- Huh?
- [Ma-kun] Yeah!
[boy on PA] The one who can go in is…
[Megumi]
They get closer to each other in there.
…the one who got the most love letters.
- Oh, here we go.
- Ruru.
[Leo] What?
- [Hikaru] You didn't know?
- [Ma-kun] I didn't.
[Hikaru]
You don't know who sent letters to who?
- [Leo] No, I don't.
- No, we do. We do, right?
[boy on PA] Ruru, please choose
the man you want to go with.
- [Ma-kun] Right now?
- [all laugh]
- [Leo] When else?
- [Ma-kun] Here and now?
[Ruru groans]
- Then?
- What?
- [Ruru laughs]
- You know.
- Shut up.
- [women laughing]
Look what he did.
- That was so cute, seriously.
- [Leo] What was?
- [Assun] So cute.
- Don't look at me.
- You made a cute face, bro.
- [Leo] Stop looking at me.
You should make it more.
The sauna. Uh…
- Who wants to go with me?
- Me!
[women laughing]
- [Ruru] Just one?
- [Ma-kun] So cute.
- Go with someone who wants it.
- True.
But since it's the first time,
I want to go with someone
I can have a deep conversation with.
- Right, who do you want that to be?
- [Leo] Oh, my God.
Shut up.
[Ruru] Mmm…
Okay, I've decided.
Let's go.
- After you.
- [Awich] See? [laughs]
- [Nagano] You were right, Awich!
- [Megumi] As expected.
- [Ari] Have fun.
- [Ma-kun] See you later.
- [Nagano] She was watching the situation.
- [Megumi] Right.
- [Ma-kun] Shall we go?
- [Ruru] Let's.
- You like saunas?
- [Ma-kun] I do.
- [Ruru] Me too.
- They're great, right?
- Don't cry. [laughing] Don't cry!
- [Ari] Oh, man, this is bad.
- I'll comfort you.
- Hey, I'm not hurt at all.
- [Ari] You look like you are.
- I'm not. I'm not hurt at all.
It's tough
to get your hopes lifted then dropped.
- [Ari] She approached you.
- [Hikaru] She did? [laughs]
Yeah, but I thought she'd choose him.
- [Ari] Oh, really?
- The moment she hesitated.
REFRESHED
[exhilarating music playing]
Wow, this is the best.
- [Megumi] This time, it's outdoors.
- [Nagamo] Oh!
- It's so open!
- [Megumi] Yes.
- Here you are.
- Hey! Wow!
- Isn't this great?
- It's amazing.
It's perfect, right?
[emcees laugh]
Wait. No, that can't be.
- Don't you think he has too many tattoos?
- [Nagano] I don't know where to look.
I mean, he has a Daruma on his stomach.
- So, why me? Why am I here?
- It's not like that.
There's a reason for this.
When we were talking about it
between the girls,
you were the most popular guy.
We all agreed on it.
We all agreed that it was you.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Oh, my God.
So, if everyone was
going to give you their letter,
I thought I should give mine to Leo,
who was the second guy
I wanted to talk to the most.
- Ah.
- So I gave it to Leo.
- So that's how it was.
- Yes.
I see.
And since we had
this opportunity in the sauna,
I thought I wanted to talk to you.
- Oh, I see. Thank you. I see.
- That's why I asked you out.
She wanted to give it to Ma-kun
but gave it to Leo, her second choice.
- She says it straight out.
- I know, right?
I thought you were pretty nice,
and I had a good impression of you.
I thought you were
the best-looking guy here at first.
- Really?
- [laughs]
Yeah. I'm saying, right now,
you're the one I'm most interested in.
Oh, I'm really happy.
I'm so happy to hear that.
- I wanted to tell you.
- Thank you. I got the message.
- What do you like? Personality, looks?
- Personality.
- Personality, huh?
- That's right.
Oh.
For what I want, I really think that
love is more important
than other things, like money.
- You're a genius.
- [laughs]
- I'm trying to say all the right things.
- Yeah, you're a genius.
- Can she really be this nice?
- [laughs]
But I have my bad side too.
- Yeah?
- Because I cheat.
- You're the type that cheats.
- I'm the type that cheats.
- [groans]
- I'm also telling you my bad side, okay?
- I see.
- Because I was only saying good things.
- [scoffs]
- I wonder why she chose to say that now.
What's her plan?
I think she wants to be loved
for who she is.
[Megumi and Nagano] Oh!
I think she's looking for
someone who can do that.
I mean, I want to have a relationship
where I don't cheat.
- I really want that. Seriously.
- You're a strong-willed person.
- Am I strong-willed? Really?
- Yeah, you are. Yeah.
- Glad to hear that.
- You have a strong sense of self.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- I like hearing that.
- Isn't that important?
I really hate it when people say
they'll accept or do something
even though they don't want to.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
- I'm the type that can't stand that stuff.
- Yeah, uh-huh, uh-huh.
You gotta have a sense of self.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
In the past, for example,
- with my ex-girlfriend…
- Mmm.
…I'd say, like,
"Let's have yakiniku to eat."
- I always do, by the way.
- Mmm.
So, when I told my ex-girlfriend,
she didn't really like yakiniku,
but she said,
"Oh, that's fine. Anything is fine."
- I hate that.
- Mmm.
- She was trying to accommodate me.
- She was kind? Oh. So what would you do?
Let's say you want to eat yakiniku
but she wants to eat sushi.
- "Get outta here."
- Oh, you're that type?
If we're not eating meat,
what's the point?
- So you're that type of guy.
- A pain in the butt.
[Nagano] Surprisingly,
we're starting to see Ma-kun's human side.
- [Megumi] He's like a domineering husband.
- [Nagano] Right, exactly.
So, honestly, how do you feel?
I'm wondering that.
Huh? Well, it's annoying for one.
- Annoying? [laughs]
- Yeah.
- I'm interested in Ma-kun, right?
- Right.
- And you're interested in Ruru.
- Yeah.
- And now, those two are there.
- That's why I'm so confused.
What the heck is she doing? Huh?
Well, this is going to shake things up.
I don't know what her intentions are
for choosing him.
- Are you gonna fight with him?
- Mmm-hmm. If he gets cocky.
- [Ruru] What? It's beautiful.
- [Ma-kun] Amazing.
- It's gorgeous.
- It's way too beautiful.
[thrilling music playing]
[squeals, laughs]
- You went under. Your hair is wet.
- This feels so good!
This is the best. Thank you.
This feels so good.
- [Tai-chan] Wonder what they talked about.
- [Ari] Yeah, I wonder.
Whatever happened, we should make sure
we all still get along.
[door opens]
[Ari] Look. He's grinning so much.
- [Tai-chan] He's back.
- [Ari] He's grinning.
- Welcome back.
- [Ma-kun] I'm back.
- Hey.
- [Ari] Why are you grinning?
[Ma-kun] I mean, anyone would grin, right?
Come on, wouldn't you?
And did you get to know each other?
[Ma-kun] Well, I won't tell you
what we talked about
since it involves her too.
Mmm.
But if you ask me
if I'm interested or not,
- I would say I'm interested.
- [Ari] Right.
[Ma-kun] I'm interested in her.
- [Ruru] I'm back.
- Hey.
- Welcome back.
- [Assun] How was it?
- No sauna magic, I'm afraid.
- What?
- [Ruru laughs]
- [Assun] Why not?
- [gasps] What?
- [Megumi] Mmm?
- [Ruru] Well, you know…
- Yeah.
[Ruru] I thought
Ma-kun seemed a bit mature, you know?
Like, he seemed calm.
I was attracted to that,
so I figured I'd ask him out to the sauna.
[Hikaru] Mmm-hmm.
But then I thought he was really childish.
Like… [sighs]
I'm really disappointed.
He's just a pretty face.
That's all he has.
It's awkward to hear you
talk bad about him like that.
[Maririn] I know.
- You're supposed to be into each other.
- This is awkward.
[closing theme song playing]